Faculty-Student Association; Records ua310
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Food Service- Financial Statements, 1973 February 28 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 18)
- Food Service- Financial Statements, 1973 March 31 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 19)
- Food Service Study, 1971 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 20)
- Food Service Supervisory Conference, 1966 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 21)
- For Auditors, 1964-1965 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 22)
- General Offices, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 23)
- Guidelines for the Selection of Officers, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 24)
- Handbooks for Employees, 1965 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 25)
- Insurance, 1964; 1966; Undated (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 26)
- Interim Statements, 1967-1970 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 27)
- "Looking to the Future with the Faculty Student Association", ca. 1965 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 28)
- Loans, 1968-1970; Undated (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 29)
- Locker, Dick, Correspondence, 1965; Undated (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 30)
- A Management Analysis for the Faculty-Student Association, 1972 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 31)
- Minority Report Representing the Views of the Undergraduate Students, 1971 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 32)
- Mohawk Property Development: A Progress Report, 1966 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 33)
- Monthly Financial Report, 1973 September (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 34)
- Monthly Financial Report, 1973 October (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 35)
- Monthly Financial Report, 1973 November (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 36)
- Monthly Financial Report, 1973 December (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 37)
- Monthly Financial Report, 1974 January (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 38)
- Monthly Financial Report, 1974 February (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 39)
- Monthly Financial Report, 1974 March (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 40)
- Monthly Financial Report, 1974 April (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 41)
- Monthly Financial Report, 1974 May (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 42)
- Monthly Financial Report, 1974 September (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 43)
- Monthly Financial Report, 1974 October (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 44)
- Monthly Financial Report, 1974 December (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 45)
- Monthly Financial Report, 1975 February (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 46)
- Monthly Financial Report, 1975 April (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 47)
- Organizational Manual, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 48)
- Outline of Material to have Available for Nelson Associates for Student-Faculty Association Corporation Study, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 49)
- Proposal for the Creation of a Student Art Gallery in the Campus Center, 1969 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 50)
- Proposal Regarding Organizational and Institutional Issues, 1970 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 51)
- Publishing Division, 1968 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 52)
- Quick View of the Operations of the Faculty-Student Association, 1967 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 53)
- Report of Management Survey, 1972 May (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 54)
- Rental Properties, 1966; Undated (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 55)
- Room and Board Rates, 1957; 1963; 1965 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 56)
- Salaries and Personnel Committee, 1972 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 57)
- Salary and Wages Procedures, 1967 January 31 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 58)
- Special Committee on Finance, 1971 February (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 59)
- Statement, 1960 June 30 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 60)
- Student Board of Finance, 1958 June (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 61)
- Student Count for Food Service, 1963 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 62)
- Study of Accounting Operations, 1966 January (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 63)
- Summary of Operations, 1971-1972; Undated (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 64-66)
- Supply and Inventory Lists, 1965-1966; 1968; Undated (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 67)
- Teachers-Albany Inc., 1954 June 30 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 68)
- Thurlow, Park and Lake Statement of Operations, 1955 June 30 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 69)
- University Bookstore, 1964-1966 (Box 4 (Faculty-Student Association Records ), Folder 70)